<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patrick King</title>
    <link>https://patrickcking.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Patrick King</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 09:50:19 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://patrickcking.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GPG Key Transition Statement</title>
      <link>https://patrickcking.com/2021/02/gpg-key-transition-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 09:50:19 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patrickcking.com/2021/02/gpg-key-transition-statement/</guid>
      <description>I have created a new GPG Key 0x944E36F397047609 and will be transitioning away from my old key. If you have signed my previous key I would appreciate signatures on my new key as well. I have included a signed transition statement below which can also be found at www.patrickcking.com/key-transition-2021-02-23.txt if you prefer to download it.
-----BEGIN PGP SIGNED MESSAGE----- Hash: SHA512 OpenPGP Key Transition Statement for Patrick King I have created a new OpenPGP key and will be transitioning away from my old key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website!</title>
      <link>https://patrickcking.com/2021/02/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:38:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patrickcking.com/2021/02/new-website/</guid>
      <description>After many years of owning www.patrickcking.com and really doing nothing with it, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that it&amp;rsquo;s time to make use of this domain. This decision comes as a time when I am preparing to leave all social media websites and I am trying to find the least disruptive way to do so. The main drive to build this site is for my contact and event pages which I hope will allow me to keep in touch with my friends and continue to organize parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://patrickcking.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patrickcking.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Below are my preferred contact methods in order of preference. Most of them are end to end encrypted allowing for greater privacy for both users.
 Matrix: @patrick:patrickcking.chat Signal: +15038054667 E-Mail: patrick@patrickcking.com  Please use PGP/MIME. My public email subkey can be found here.   Keybase: keybase://chat/king SMS Text Message Phone Calls  Other forms of communication should be encrypted with my GPG public key (0x2A590EC935F55DB1) if you want our communication to remain private.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://patrickcking.com/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://patrickcking.com/events/</guid>
      <description>As I&amp;rsquo;m deploying this website we are still in the middle of the Covid-19 pandemic so I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished this page yet. However, eventually there will sign-up form here so you can be emailed whenever I host and event or party!
 This page&amp;rsquo;s markdown can be verified with this signature and it&amp;rsquo;s HTML can be verified with this signature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
